Good to meet you, man.
Good to meet you, sir.
All right, so I kind of want to start
at the basics or the foundation.
I want to see what-
Can I just check?
Yes.
Are you a fascist?
No.
Okay.
I describe myself as, I think, just a Christian.
Fair enough.
I'm a devout Christian.
Good to hear.
So, I want to start, like, what is your connection
to the Constitution and why do you love it so much?
Like, what makes it so important that Trump
would defy something like the Constitution to you personally?
Great questions.
My first connection is I'm an American citizen.
I naturalized American citizen.
Took a pledge to this country, to the Constitution.
As a previous speaker has said,
Constitution's not perfect.
A lot of things I don't like about it.
I don't like the Second Amendment.
There's various amendments.
I don't like the way the Senate is set up.
I'm sure there's things you don't like
about the Constitution.
The difference is, I don't think you can just
illegally defy the Constitution.
I don't think each and everyone
is going to make up whatever we want.
Certainly presidents who are elected with an oath, right?
Donald Trump took an oath to preserve, protect,
and defend the Constitution.
And now when he's asked on television,
isn't it your job to uphold the Constitution?
He said on NBC, I don't know, which goes against his oath.
And I'm identifying specific amendments
where he is violating.
He's only six months into his presidency
defying the First Amendment, the Fourth Amendment,
the Fifth Amendment, the 14th Amendment.
He wants to defy the 22nd Amendment
and be president for a third term.
This is the problem we have right now.
Free speech is under assault.
The free press is under assault.
Due process is under assault.
The right to be in your home
and not be invaded by federal agents,
the Fourth Amendment, is under assault.
So that, for me, is a problem.
Okay.
Well, I'd like to start to say
I really don't find the Constitution that important.
I find it to be like a 300-year-old document.
And it was created to defy the country
that subjugated your ancestors in India.
And then your parents probably moved from India to Britain.
And then you move here to tell us
that we should listen to a piece of paper
that you were never even connected to to begin with.
So I want to say, like, if I don't care about it,
why do you care about it so much?
How do you run a country
without any kind of laws or due process?
And by the way, you do care about it,
because without the First Amendment,
you wouldn't be sitting here.
Oh, I agree with the First Amendment.
So do you agree with Donald Trump's crackdown
on the First Amendment?
He's imprisoning people for their speech.
He's threatening free speech media organizations.
He's threatening peaceable assembly.
These are all rights under the First Amendment.
Why aren't you bothered by that
as a conservative who claims to love the First Amendment?
So I actually, I don't like the First Amendment.
I like free speech.
The First Amendment is what guarantees free speech.
I'm from the UK, by the way.
I'm from the UK, which is a democracy.
We don't have the First Amendment.
No, because that's one of the things
I do like about the Constitution.
I wish the UK did have a First Amendment.
I'm a journalist.
Arrested for praying outside abortion clinics
and stuff like that, right?
So you're opposed to people
being arrested for speech crimes, I assume.
It depends what it is.
If it's like the people-
Oh, so you're like one of the previous speakers.
As long as it's someone who agrees with you,
you don't mind the crackdown.
No, no, no, I support-
Either we consistently support principles or we don't.
I support free speech 100%.
Okay.
So do you think Donald Trump
is defying the Constitution
by cracking down on the First Amendment?
So I think he's cracking down on free speech
like the deportation of Mahmoud Khalil, who's-
Who was just released from prison by a judge
saying his First Amendment rights were violated.
And I agree with the judge
and I disagree with Trump deporting them.
But I think that's more a matter of free speech
and not the Constitution.
I think that's pedantry at this moment.
I think you've conceded
that he is cracking down on free speech,
which is the First Amendment.
So he is defying the Constitution.
So it's a pleasure to be in agreement with you, sir.
All right, pause.
You've been voted out by the majority.
Please return to your seats.
All right, thank you very much.
Thank you.